indiansinkuwait.com 2008-02-16

# Indians in Kuwait - A Complete Web Portal for Indians in Kuwait

> **Our Commitment**  
>  indiansinkuwat.com is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information secure. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, we are fully disclosing our privacy practices. We encourage you to read our privacy statement to understand what types of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information. 
> 
> **Information collected by indiansinkuwat.com and how it is used**  
>  indiansinkuwat.com only collects the necessary personally identifiable information in order to respond to your requests for our customized services. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, first and last name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number, and any other information that itself identifies or when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual. 
> 
> This website does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. indiansinkuwat.com and its service partners use your personally identifiable information to operate the sites and services and to inform you of new features, services, and products from indiansinkuwat.com and its affiliates. 
> 
> indiansinkuwat.com may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site's service but are not necessary to its operation (an "Extended Service"). If indiansinkuwat.com intends to use personally identifiable information for an Extended Service, the indiansinkuwat.com site will provide you with the ability and requisite instructions to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from indiansinkuwat.com by following the instructions on the mail. 
> 
> indiansinkuwat.com may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the site or its owners; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the site-owners, the site or the users of indiansinkuwat.com, and (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of indiansinkuwat.com, the site, its owners, or the public. 
> 
> **User/member interaction features**  
>  indiansinkuwat.com has many features that provide for users/members to disclose their identities and communicate with other users/members. Your use of such features and disclosure of any personal details (e.g. e-mail address) by you through these features are at your sole risk and indiansinkuwat.com accepts no responsibility for the same. However, if your privacy has been intruded as a result of participating in such features, you could notify us by e-mail at privacy@indiansinkuwat.com. 
> 
> **Other Websites**  
>  The indiansinkuwat.com site contains links to other websites. indiansinkuwat.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 
> 
> **Notify Us**  
>  If at any time you believe that indiansinkuwat.com or its users/members have not adhered to these principles, please notify indiansinkuwat.com by e-mail at privacy@indiansinkuwat.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.   
>
